Let the manhunt begin.
The Breed is a thriller, horror film directed by Nicholas Mastandrea.
Brothers John and Matt have inherited an island cabin
from their recently deceased uncle.
Along with Matt's girlfriend, Nicki, and other mutual friends, the
siblings travel to the cabin for a relaxing weekend getaway.
But, not long after arriving, the group is besieged by ravenous dogs.
They watch in horror as another vacationer, Luke, is eaten alive.
Soon, they discover a training facility where the dogs have been bred to kill.
Nicki, played by Michelle Rodriguez.
Sara, played by Taryn Manning.
Matt, played by Eric Lively.
John, played by Oliver Hudson.
Noah, played by Hill Harper.
Luke, played by Nick Boraine.
The Breed is a 2006 horror drama film that is directed by Nicholas Mastandrea.
Having marked Mastandrea's directorial debut, the film features two brothers and their friends who travel to an
island cabin the brothers inherited from their recently deceased uncle for a relaxing weekend getaway.
However, the group is besieged by ravenous genetically enhanced dogs bred
to kill at an abandoned training facility on the island.
Critic reviews were generally negative.
The film explores themes of exotic island, loss of loved
one, animal attack, baseball bat, vacation.
The tone is dark and intense.